今天我们要讨论一个问题，这实际上是机器人视觉的核心。
Today we're going to talk about a problem, which is really at the heart of robotic vision.
机器人是相对简单的机器。如果我们考虑工业机器人的情况，
Robots are relatively simple machines. If we consider the case of an industrial robot,
一个有六个关节，我们可以通过简单地指定六个速度来控制它
one that's got six joints, we can control that by simply specifying six velocities or
速度。我们指定每个电机的速度，机器人可以做任何动作。
speeds. We specify the speed of each of its motors and the robot can do any kind of action.
轮式移动机器人，我们通过简单地指定两个速度来控制;这就是速度
A wheeled mobile robot, we control by specifying simply two velocities; that's the velocity
它向前行驶的速度和转弯的速度。所以我们遇到了问题
at which it drives forward and the velocity at which is turns. So we've got a problem
因为从相机发出的数据量大约是数百万的数量级
because the amount of data that comes out of a camera is of the order of 10's of millions
每秒像素数;每秒数百万的数字。但我们只需要两个或者
of pixels per second; 10's of millions of numbers per second. But we need only two or
六，极少数，以实际控制机器人。这就像试着喝酒
six, a very small number, in order to actually control the robot. It's like trying to drink
从消防水带出来;来自相机的大量数据，少量的
out of a fire hose; massive amount of data coming out of the camera, small amount of
控制机器人所需的数据。因此，为了解决这个问题，我们执行了一项技术
data needed to control the robot. So to get around this problem we perform a technique
被称为“特征提取”，我们要做的就是找到图像的本质;
called "Feature Extraction" and what we're trying to do is find the essence of the image;
图像中最重要的信息，我们可以直接喂我们的机器人。
the most important information in the image, we can feed directly to our robot.